

hello@dianenguyen.ca • https://dianenguyen.ca • San Francisco

ABOUT

A front end designer & developer originally based in Vancouver and now in San Francisco, with an immense desire to enhance the experience of the things she loves so that others can fall in love with them, too. Particularly in love with music & video games.

EDUCATION

2013 - BCIT: BC Institute of Technology 2008 - Fraser Heights Secondary 2015 Digital Design and Development 2013 Secondary School

WORK EXPERIENCE

MONSTERCAT • WEB DESIGNER/DEVELOPER

2018 - 2022

- Designed responsive, user friendly and accessible web interfaces in Figma
- Both collaborated with team and worked independently to implement designs using HTML, CSS, and JS
- Worked with clients and company employees to identify pain points within existing tools
- Works include branding website, marketing campaigns, music web app, and internal software used by company and music artists (I.E. music distribution, artist payments, and invoicing)

BOWERY CREATIVE • WEB DESIGNER/DEVELOPER

2017 - 2018

- Designed stylescapes for clients to identify which styles best suit their needs
- Developed websites for clients and businesses on WordPress, Squarespace and Shopify (I.E. lead generation, product shops, and educational programs)

IMMORTALS GG • WEB DESIGNER/DEVELOPER

2016 - 2018

- Mocked up multipage website for a professional Esports organization
- Used WordPress to develop template and widgets
- Website featured team roster, tournament schedules, ecommerce, news, and careers board
- Designed marketing assets, newsletter templates, and retouched team photos